db.question.insertMany([{
Entertainment:{
	Easy:[
		{Question:"How many players per team are there in court in handball?",Answer: "7",choiceA: "6",choiceB: "7",choiceC: "8",choiceD: "9"},
		{Question:"How many squares are there in a chess board?",Answer: "64",choiceA: "48",choiceB: "56",choiceC: "64",choiceD: "72"},
		{Question:"What is the name given to the NFL final?",Answer: "Super Bowl",choiceA: "Super Bowl",choiceB: "World Cup",choiceC: "Wimbledon",choiceD: "The Masters"},
		{Question:"When did the FIFA World Cup take place in the USA?",Answer: "1994",choiceA: "1991",choiceB: "1992",choiceC: "1993",choiceD: "1994"},
		{Question:"",Answer: "",choiceA: "",choiceB: "",choiceC: "",choiceD: ""},
  ],
	Medium:[
		{Question:"The tiger Hodori was the mascot of which Olympic Games?",Answer: "Seoul 88 Olympic Games",choiceA: "Seoul 84 Olympic Games",choiceB: "Seoul 86 Olympic Games",choiceC: "Seoul 88 Olympic Games",choiceD: "Seoul 90 Olympic Games"},
		{Question:"Swords are used in which of the following martial arts?",Answer: "Ninjutsu",choiceA: "Ninjutsu",choiceB: "Chijutsu",choiceC: "Jujutsu",choiceD: "Chajutsu"},
		{Question:"What year were the first modern Olympics Games held?",Answer: "1896",choiceA: "1894",choiceB: "1896",choiceC: "1898",choiceD: "1900"},
		{Question:"What country is Taekwondo originally from?",Answer: "Korea",choiceA: "China",choiceB: "Japan",choiceC: "Thailand",choiceD: "Korea"},
		{Question:"Who won the Formula One Worldâ€™s Driver Championship in 2005 and 2006?",Answer: "Fernando Alonso",choiceA: "Paavo Nurmi",choiceB: "Fernando Alonso",choiceC: "Mark Spitz",choiceD: "Carl Lewis"},
  ],
	Difficult:[
		{Question:"From which country is the athlete Maria Mutola, who won her eighth world title in Paris in 2003?",Answer: "Mozambique",choiceA: "Turkmenistan",choiceB: "Pakistan",choiceC: "Dubai",choiceD: "Mozambique"},
		{Question:"Anna Kournikova won the doubles competition of the Australian Open of 1999. What swiss player was her partner?",Answer: "Martina Hingis",choiceA: "Mal Meninga",choiceB: "Mal Meningo",choiceC: "Martina Hingis",choiceD: "Martina Hingos"},
		{Question:"How many goals did Germany score in the 2014 World Cup Against Brazil?",Answer: "7",choiceA: "4",choiceB: "5",choiceC: "6",choiceD: "7"},
		{Question:"How many games were disputed in the longest match in the history of Wimbledon?",Answer: "183",choiceA: "183",choiceB: "184",choiceC: "185",choiceD: "186"},
		{Question:"Where were the first Pan American Games celebrated, in 1951?",Answer: "Buenos Aires",choiceA: "Canada",choiceB: "Kazakhstan",choiceC: "Buenos Aires",choiceD: "Argentina"},
  ]
  }
}])
